[{"answer": "It was really, I found, horrifying, because I watched the whole thing.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "We have to as a nation examine our souls and say, how did we come to this?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "That's problem.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "If you can't get angry over the cold-blooded murder of 20 school children age 6 and 7 years old, when the hell do you get angry?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "What would you think?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Yes, I think the NRA missed a huge opportunity.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "-- when your heard the address by Wayne LaPierre?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I'm not.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Are you a member of the NRA yourself or?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Right, when you have such a tragedy like we did, it was such a dark day for this nation.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "What is your view about the specific campaign which I have been pursuing and the president is pursuing and others are pursuing which is not about banning guns, it's about banning assault weapons, getting the kind of weapons which can massacre school classrooms, these military-style machines, getting those off the streets?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "That's a good question.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "You think assault weapons should be banned or not?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "The particular assault weapon that massacred the children at the Sandy Hook School, was the same one used at the Oregon shopping mall mass shooting and in Aurora in the movie theater.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Please?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "What I never hear back from anyone who defends them is what other purpose can they possibly have than mass slaughter?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "I don't see how video games can contribute to violence in that manner, especially when most video games is emulate real life.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "What is your view about that?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "First of all, this is not as rare as people might think.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "What is the answer?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Piers, this is what's going to change it.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "What is going to change this culture?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Well, of course.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "But as she said, people should be trained for these use, right?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Here's what I think: you have to try.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "What law do you propose that would have stopped this?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Why don't you tell me, Mr. Lott?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "There's a reason --", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "How many bullets can it fire in a second?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "The point --", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "How many bullets does the AR 15 fire a second?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I'm going to answer your first question.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Do you want to answer or not?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "The point is --", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "How many bullets does it fire a second?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "You will lose lives.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Can you answer the question or not?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I think your estimate is high.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "But I understand your passion, having stood on too many street corners, seen too many bodies, seen the kind of weapons we're pulling of the streets.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "If you were trying to debate this in a more rational way than I appear capable of, what would you do?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "There are three points that I think need to be raised.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "What do you think of this debate?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "You know, I think getting rid of the assault weapons, you know, it is not a perfect bill, but we will never be able to legislate against evil.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Do you want to see these assault rifles just gone?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I absolutely believe in banning those weapons.", "docId": "121221pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 606}]